# Dávid HOROV

+421 904 247 916Swww.davidhorov.com✓ contact@davidhorov.com✓ Slovakia

Frontend developer

Prague Labs

12/2020 - Present

Time-Line

University of Porto
Computer Science and
Project Management
02/2016 - 07/2016

Education

Work Experience

University of Baelaric Islands
Computer Science
and Engineering
2017 - 2020
02/2018 - 07/2018

Frontend developer
Trisbee

Masaryk University Computer Science 2014 - 2017 Frontend developer Mautilus 11/2016 - 11/2017

Web application developer Freelancer 12/2017 - 01/2020

01/2020 - 1

### Life Philosophy

"Always turn a negative situation into a positive situation"

#### About me

I am 27 years old remote front-end React developer with a master's degree from Faculty of Informatics, Masaryk University in Brno. I am focused on developing React/Next.js applications, but willing to learn new technologies as well.

### My Passions



Traveling



Reading, Studying



Sport



Meeting people



Cooking

#### Soft Skills



# Programming Skills

HTML5, CSS3, React

planning

Next.js

TypeScript

Bootstrap, SAAS, LEES, SC

Vue.js, SQL, Bash

## Industry Skills

- Responsive development, UX/UI
- App performance improvements
- Figma, xD, A/B testing
- GIT, Jira, Zapier, Optimize
- REST, GRPC, WebSockets, JSON, XML

#### My Numbers

12 Months studying abroad	24+ Completed projects
74	8+
Completed courses at the university	Years working in computer science

# My Certificates

Git, React, HTML, CSS, JSON (LinkedIn)

Dean's award - Master thesis

State examination of computer administration and corespondency

IBM award - best web application

Wordprocessing - competitions



# Linkedin profile

